Guide to the Vassar College Facilities Operations Records, 1800s-2021 (bulk 1908-1999)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series II. Plans, 1800s - 2010
  - Swift Hall (Infirmary), 1899-1968
    - [Plans] Swift Hall, 1900, 1934 (Roll Box 322)
    - [Plans] Swift Hall, 1968 (Roll Box 218)
    - [Plans] Swift Hall, undated (Map Case - Drawer 132)
  - Taylor Hall, 1911 - circa 1980s
    - [Plans] Academic Buildings - Proposed Music and Art Building (Folder 2 of 3), 1911; (3 items) (Map Case - Drawer 58)
    - [Plans] Academic Buildings - Proposed Music and Art Building (Folder 3 of 3), 1911-1930, undated (Map Case - Drawer 60)
    - [Plans] Taylor, 1912 (Roll Box 205)
    - [Plans] Taylor Hall - Proposed Additions, [1912?]-1935; (11 items) (Map Case - Drawer 57)
    - [Plans] Art Building, 1913 (Roll Box 205)
    - [Plans] Taylor Library Addition, 1934-1935 (Roll Box 195)
    - [Plans] Taylor Alterations, 1961 (Roll Box 204)
    - [Plans] Taylor/Library Alterations, 1961-1963 (Roll Boxes 197-198)
    - [Plans] Taylor Hall Alterations, 1962 (Roll Box 192)
    - [Plans] Taylor, 1962 (Roll Box 203)
    - [Plans] Vassar College Art Gallery and Art Department, Peter Rose, circa 1980s (Roll Box 200)
    - [Plans] Taylor Hall - Proposed Additions, undated (Map Case - Drawer 133)
  - Utilities - Electric, 1930-1989
    - [Plans] Campus Electrical System Proposed Service, 1930 (Roll Box 314)
    - [Plans] Campus Electrical System DC to AC Conversion, circa 1955-1956 (Roll Box 300-307)
    - [Plans] Electrical Distribution Schematic, 1957 (Roll Box 37)
    - [Plans] Campus Electrical Schematic, 1968 (Roll Box 13)
    - [Plans] Vassar College Electrical Distribution, 1968 (Roll Box 234)
    - [Plans] "Campus Electrical Distribution Schematic", 1973 (Roll Box 33)
    - [Plans] Vassar College Electrical Distribution, revised, 1985 (Roll Box 234)
    - [Plans] Campus Electrical Distribution Schematic, 1989 (Roll Box 33)
    - [Plans] Miscellaneous Electrical Plans, undated (Roll Box 235)
    - [Plans] Campus Electrical Manhole Details, undated (Roll Box 146)
  - Utilities - Heating and Cooling, 1927-1989
    - [Plans] Heating, 1927 (Roll Box 342)
    - [Plans] Vassar College Steam Connections Unit 5, 1932 (Roll Box 261)
    - [Plans] "Campus Gas Distribution Schematic", 1943 (Roll Box 33)
    - [Plans] Campus Utilities Renovation Phase 2 - "New Steam", 1966 (Roll Box 232)
    - [Plans] Steam System, circa 1968 (Roll Box 40)
    - [Plans] Chilled Water Piping System, 1975 (Roll Box 256)
    - [Plans] Vassar College Loop Feed, 1989 (Roll Box 234)
    - [Plans] Powerhouse "New Power Header", undated (Roll Box 45)
    - [Plans] "Plans of Gas Holder", undated (Roll Box 45)
  - Utilities - Miscellaneous, 1909-1971
    - [Plans] Map showing sewers, steam ducts, water, gas, and electrical conduits, 1909; (2 copies) (Map Case - Drawer 57)
    - [Plans] "Combined Service Map - Timmis", 1911 (Roll Box 38)
    - [Plans] "Breechings. Sprague and Slochum", 1916-1917 (Roll Box 44)
    - [Plans] "Vaccuum Pump Layout", 1926 (Roll Box 49)
    - [Plans] "Blower", 1928 (Roll Box 66)
    - [Plans] Campus Utilities Renovation Phase 1, 1965 (Roll Box 235)
    - [Plans] "Utilities Renovation Phase 4", 1968 (Roll Box 34)
    - [Plans] "Utilities Renovation Raymond Avenue", 1971 (Roll Box 36)
    - [Plans] "Turbo Generator Piping Diagram", undated (Roll Box 41)
    - [Plans] Fire maps, alarms, sprinklers, undated (Map Case - Drawer 87)
    - [Plans] Miscellaneous Utility Schematics, undated (Roll Box 237)
    - [Plans] Sewer disposal plans, undated (Map Case - Drawer 57)
    - [Plans] Unidentified Utilities, undated (Roll Box 42)
    - [Plans] Utilities, undated (Map Case - Drawer 139)
    - [Plans] Utilities - Misc, undated (Roll Box 338)
    - [Plans] Various Steam, Electrical, and Telephone Schematics, undated (Roll Box 235)
    - [Plans] Vassar College Grounds Schematic Survey with Costs - "Original Exists in Library", undated (Roll Box 236)
  - Vogelstein Center for Drama and Film (Avery Hall, Calisthenium and Riding Academy), 1874-1971
    - [Plans] Avery Hall - Architectural Drawings, 1874; (4 items) (Map Case - Drawer 46)
    - [Plans] Avery Hall, 1912 (Roll Box 59)
    - [Plans] Avery Hall, 1918 (Roll Box 341)
    - [Plans] Avery Hall Basement, 1931 (Roll Box 61)
    - [Plans] Avery Hall "Experimental Theater", 1933 (Roll Box 58)
    - [Plans] Avery Hall, circa 1934-1935, 1952 (Roll Boxes 56-58)
    - [Plans] "Avery Hall Classical Museum", 1938 (Roll Box 59)
    - [Plans] Avery, 1969 (Roll Box 323)
    - [Plans] [Miscellaneous Experimental Theater – Avery Hall], 1971 (Roll Box 295)
    - [Plans] Avery Hall, undated (Map Case - Drawer 65)
    - [Plans] Negative Print "Auditorium Building", undated (Roll Box 59)
    - [Plans] Vogelstein Center for Drama and Film, undated (Map Case - Drawer 80)
    - [Plans] Vogelstein Center for Drama and Film, undated (Map Case - Drawer 81)
  - Wimpfheimer Nursery School, 1926 - circa 1927
    - [Plans] "Nursery School", 1926 (Roll Box 56)
    - [Plans] Proposed Nursery School, circa 1927; (5 copies) (Map Case - Drawer 57)
    - [Plans] Wimpfheimer Nursery School, undated (Map Case - Drawer 137)
  - Miscellaneous Building Plans, 1909-2004
    - [Plans] Ice Rink, 1909 (Roll Box 344)
    - [Plans] Ice House, 1911 (Roll Box 83)
    - [Plans] Guide post, 1916 Dec; (1 item) (Map Case - Drawer 57)
    - [Plans] "Schedule of Bldgs.", signed by George Gliss, 1917 (Roll Box 318)
    - [Plans] Concrete Roads, John Ogden, 1922 (Roll Box 334)
    - [Plans] Plan for Location of New Buildings, 1923 Nov (Map Case - Drawer 57)
    - [Plans] Proposed Plan for Delivery Hall, 1937; (1 item) (Map Case - Drawer 57)
    - [Plans] New Conservatory, 1941 (Map Case - Drawer 83)
    - [Plans] "Cottage Street property, 1903", 1943; (photocopy) (Map Case - Drawer 57)
    - [Plans] Academic Buildings - Proposed Plant Laboratory (Folder 1 of 3), [1946]; (1 item) (Map Case - Drawer 58)
    - [Plans] Urban Center, 1970 (Roll Box 316)
    - [Plans] Proposed Campus Circulation Pattern, 1972 (Roll Box 324)
    - [Plans] Marina Site, 1979 (Roll Box 325)
    - [Plans] Topographical Map of Lands to be Developed by the City of Poughkeepsie, 1980 (Roll Box 326)
    - [Plans] Sun Tempered Homes, 1984 (Roll Box 293)
    - [Plans] Boardman Road Annex Library, 1986-2004 (Map Case - Drawer 68)
    - [Plans] Class of 1963 Gate, Sasaki, 1989 (Roll Boxes 316-317)
    - [Plans] "Ships Ladder by Stage", 1990 (Roll Box 59)
    - [Plans] Class of 1963 Gate, Sasaki, 1990 (Roll Box 322)
    - [Plans] "Dutchess County Music Building" Allen and Collens, undated (Roll Box 59)
    - [Plans] "Proposed Changes in Campus Circulation", Molly S. Drysdale, undated (Roll Box 317)
    - [Plans] "Proposed Dutchess County Music Building" Allen and Collens, undated (Roll Box 58)
    - [Plans] "Proposed Music Hall" Allen and Collens, undated (Roll Box 57)
    - [Plans] Class of 1963 Gate, undated (Map Case - Drawer 88)
    - [Plans] College Store, undated (Map Case - Drawer 75)
    - [Plans] Gate Lodge, undated (Roll Box 248)
    - [Plans] Hughes Farmhouse, undated (Roll Box 264)
    - [Plans] Ice House, undated (Roll Box 272)
    - [Plans] Ice House, undated (Roll Box 71)
    - [Plans] Ice Room, undated (Roll Box 31)
    - [Plans] Plans for Auditorium, Jared, St. John, LaDow, undated (Roll Box 240)
    - [Plans] Proposed memorial gate for Vassar College, undated; (1 item) (Map Case - Drawer 57)
    - [Plans] Pump Room, undated (Roll Box 42)
    - [Plans] Vassar Tower Room, undated (Roll Box 340)
  - Unidentified and Unprocessed Plans, 1924-1975, undated
    - [Plans] Unidentified Building, Ceiling Plan, 1924 (Roll Box 17)
    - [Plans] Unidentified, 1975 (Roll Box 15)
    - [Plans] Miscellaneous, undated (Roll Boxes 327-331)
    - [Plans] Miscellaneous Historic plans, undated (Map Case - Drawer 139)
    - [Plans] Miscellaneous Photocopies of Larger Plans, undated (Roll Box 324)
    - [Plans] Miscellaneous plans, undated (Map Case - Drawer 138)
    - [Plans] Miscellaneous plans, undated (Roll Box 357)
    - [Plans] Miscellaneous, mylar, undated (Roll Box 332)
    - [Plans] Unidentified, undated (Roll Box 17)
    - [Plans] Unidentified, undated (Roll Box 321)
    - [Plans] Unidentified Auditorium, Drafted by Light America, Mark Vassallo, Sunny Sonnefeld, undated (Roll Box 163)
    - [Plans] Unknown Allen and Collens project, undated (Roll Box 67)
    - Additional loose, unprocessed plans, undated